Darling, Darling!
Sailing
on the
cobalt blue!
The clouds float above the sea!
Hanging out
just me and you!
Our time is now and soon you'll see!
Smile with all your heart as you go
past the problems that await you!
Keep your hopes alive!
Never look down upon yourself!
Just cast a magic spell!
You will get through!
Crazy, crazy rainbow!
Star, twinkle, twinkle!
Rainbow star!
Fast beats!
Premonitions!
Just like the colors from
all the rainbow beams!
Crazy, crazy rainbow! Star!
Come with me and we'll go far!
We're just fallen angels!
Shooting arrows into our hopeful dreams!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
I'm a crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle rainbow star!
Within the cobalt blue!
Seven colors will come to our surprise!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle rainbow star!
Abandon all your worries!
Your troubles show through
the mirror of your eyes!
Let me comfort you, my love!
I'll hold your time within my glove!
We sure are fallen angels!
Just singing our hearts
all out from up above!
Dying, dying!
Crazy, crazy hippo star!
I'm a crazy hippo star!
This is one of our former chefs.
I hope you enjoy your stay at
the Maritime Restaurant Baratier?
Former home of Black Lake Sanji, the
infamous cook with a 77 million fairy bounty.
It looks just like him, I swear.
I propose a toast.
Raise your glasses.
Or the biggest name in all of East
Blue, with a bounty of 300 million.
Your friend Luffy.
Cheers!
Quiet down, the whole lot of you.
Have you fools no shame?
To me!
That's enough!
It's useless.
No one listens to what
the mayor says anymore.
What a cute pet.
Lucy must be having so much fun out there.
And it looks like he's made
some wonderful friends as well.
You call those thugs friends?
They're criminals!
Our town gave birth to a wanted criminal
that turned against the whole world.
And what kind of pirate is crazy enough
to declare war on the darn government?
That's a good question.
Garp needs to clean up this mess.
If he hadn't left his
grandson here on this island,
none of this would have happened.
That family's been crazy
for three generations.
I wonder if Dada knows
about all this. To Luffy!
I said quiet down, didn't I?
Sniper King.
The king of the snipers. You're right.
There's no doubt about it.
That's Usopp.
I told you.
You got the captain's nose, right?
Mm-hmm.
All the people in the
village didn't believe us.
He's worth 30 million.
Even if no one else could,
we knew you'd recognize him.
Now everyone in the world
can know how awesome he is.
The captain has the power
to make lies the truth.
All you gotta do is believe.
Don't know where he got
it, but that mask is cool.
Let's see if we can make
our own out of clay.
Hey, Kaya, where are you going?
I should get back to my
medical studies, that's all.
I have to become a good
doctor as soon as I can.
That way, if Usopp comes back here
injured after all his adventures,
I know I'll be able to fix him up.
Man, the captain sure is lucky, huh?
But I'm going to beat him up
if he ever makes Kaia sad.
Me too.
Master, is it true that Pirate Hunter
Zoro used to study at this school too?
Why, yes, that is true.
But I don't want you to
see him as a role model.
You understand?
Oh, why not?
He's so awesome.
Teach us to be pirates too,
so we can be strong like him.
I didn't teach him or
anyone else to be a pirate.
I don't believe that.
Are you lying to us, Master?
You never can tell quite
how they'll turn out.
I was surprised to hear about
what happened on Eni's lobby.
But I'm sure there isn't a speck of
doubt in your heart, right, Zoro?
No matter what kind of person you become,
all I want is for you to cherish
your own way of the sword.
Hey, Genzo!
I brought some tangerines.
Again, Nojiko?
I keep telling you I can
buy them in the store.
No need to be uptight about it.
Just take them.
Besides, you're like a
father to me and Nami.
I wouldn't dream of charging you.
If you insist.
What are you up to?
Hmm?
Oh, uh...
I've been trying to file a complaint to
Navy headquarters with
the transponder snail,
but they won't pick up the line.
A complaint?
To the Navy? That's right.
Do they really think
they can distribute such
an explicit wanted poster
all over the world?
At this rate, she'll have more marriage
suitors than bounty hunters after her.
Well, you seem to like the picture at
least, seeing as you blew it up so big.
I wouldn't let it get to you.
After all, at least you know
they kept their promise.
I know Lamy's going away with you, but if
any of you ever do anything to hurt her,
I will kill you.
That smile is all the proof we need.
Well, I suppose so, but I'd rather
she stop being a pirate. Oh, yeah?
You want to take that smile away?
Of course not!
That's not what I meant at all!
Dr. Kureha.
Dalton, what did you call
me down here for, huh?
I'm a very busy woman, you know.
Well, I'm sorry to trouble you, but when
you see these, I think you'll understand.
Not gonna ask me the
secret to my eternal youth?
Oh, and by the way, Dalton,
since you're the king and all, don't
you think you should live in the castle?
I'll rent a room out to you.
I've stayed in this village for so
long that I think I prefer it here.
I also prefer to have
chestnuts with my rice.
Well, if it isn't the Straw Hat
kid and all his little friends.
Their new wanted poster
showed up after that incident.
In Enies Lobby.
Chopper, I'm sure the amount
is some sort of mistake.
Seeing his face again is worth
all the berries in the world.
That's good as long as he's happy.
That's all I need.
Unbelievable.
Nico Robin, what in the world is Miss
All Sunday doing on Luffy's crew?
I knew there was something mysterious about
that woman, but this is quite the shock.
If this news reaches Princess Vivi,
I can only imagine how
disheartened she would be?
Oh, don't worry.
I already heard about that.
It's no big deal, though.
It's not a big deal.
I thought you of all
people would be shocked.
Even when you're as close
to Luke Lee as I was,
you can never quite
tell what he's thinking.
Whether I understand his reasoning or not,
I still believe in everything he does.
Because I know that he's going to
be king of the pirates one day.
The best we can do is
respect his decisions.
How forgiving.
You've turned into such a fine
young lady, Princess Vivi.
Hey, it's nothing to cry about.
Our forces have triumphed in Centaurion.
We did it.
Another kingdom has fallen.
We're on a roll, huh?
We had a big victory
in the North Blue, too.
This is war.
Even in victory, we must be humble.
Of course, sir.
I'm sorry.
What is this? Huh?
The posters?
They're for the Straw Hat Pirates.
They're the ones who took
out Crocodile and Alabasta.
They recently caused a big
incident at Eni's Lobby, too.
The government can't afford
to ignore them anymore.
After their recent actions, their total
bounty jumped to 666 million and 50 berries.
Also, their captain is Vice
Admiral Garp's grandson.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
I'm going to get some fresh air.
Follow your own beliefs to the end, Luffy.
With a will such as
yours and a little luck!
The masses may learn to
question this world after all?
Ride the winds of change, my son!
That day you and I meet will
come soon enough, I'm sure.
Three days before the Straw Hat
Pirates new bounties shocked the world!
Another history changing of it was
about to occur not far from Water 7!
This is Bonero Island,
a small settlement that
will soon be turned
upside down in a duel
between fire and shadow.
Whoa!
What do you know?
It's Commander Ace!
You have no right to call me that anymore.
Use that title with respect,
but don't use it at all.
I won't have you mock me.
Ooh, so this is the famous Fire Fist Ace.
Yep, that's me. You guessed it.
So this is your crew.
It looks like you've
become a captain now, huh?
Captain Marshall D.
Teach of the Blackbeard Pirates.
Yeah, come on a slight enough.
It's good to see you again.
What brings you here?
You weren't looking for me, were you?
Let's stop beating around
the bush now, shall we?
Even if you play dumb, I
know you're a crafty bastard.
There's only one reason for me to
be here, and you know what it is.
Fine, have it your way.
But there's one question
I'd like to ask first.
Instead of fighting, why don't
you become a member of my crew?
I have the perfect plan
to rise to the top.
If you stick with me, I
swear we can rule the world.
Whitebeard's days are
numbered and you know it.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates. First,
I'm headed off to Water
7 to kill Straw Hat
Luffy as a special gift
to the world government.
Wouldn't hurt to have
you along for the fun.
Luffy, huh?
You're out of your mind.
Oh, you know him?
Of course I know him, you sack of crap.
I'm not going to let you
kill my little brother.
And I'm not joining your crew.
You can take your little
offer and shove it up your...
Well, you get it.
Looks like you need to teach
your crew some manners, Captain.
Fire gun!
Flyer Filler!
Oh, Garbertus!
Both of you stay out of this fight!
Until you get stronger, this
guy is out of your league!
Do you hear me?
Oh, sorry!
Fly or bear!
Are you okay?
Captain!
Here.
Get off of me, I'm fine.
Just step back.
All righty.
I get it.
You want to finish me, don't you?
The murder of a fellow Gourmet
is a serious crime, after all.
And yes, I killed 4th Division
Commander Thatcher with my own hands,
but there wasn't any other choice.
It wasn't personal, but he had the
Devil Fruit I'd been searching for.
You know the rules on Whitebeard's ship,
whoever finds one of those gets to eat it.
I memorized the shapes and colors of all
the devil's fruits that they discovered,
so I knew that was the one I needed.
Whether I liked it or not, I spent decades
biding my time on Whitebeard's ship,
because that was the best shot I had
at finding that one single fruit.
But just when I thought
there was no hope left,
there it was, right in
the hand of my friend.
Then you murdered him in cold blood
and stole it, without a second thought.
Bad luck for him.
There's no other way.
This ability has chosen me.
And its powers may be the
strongest man in the world.
Watch.
Even among the Logia fruits,
there's nothing quite like it.
Ace, your body is made of fire, right?
My body is darkness.
Look, it's that weird
black smoke from before!
I thought those pirates were leaving.
What are we gonna do now?
I don't know what they
want, but it can't be good.
They're gonna wreck the
entire town at this rate!
Well, we sure can't stop them.
It's best just to run away!
Darkness...
You'll see soon enough, Commander Ace.
I think you'll want to
reconsider my offer.
In the history of all Devilfruits,
this is said to be the most
dangerous power of them all!
The Logia-type Dark Darkfruit!
In other words, I've
become a Darkness man!
I'll give you a taste of its power!
I wouldn't blink if I were
you stop yapping and do it
Now ain't the time for
a nap captain's on a
rampage if we don't hide
till it out of here.
He'll kill us
Look, it's crawling on the ground.
It keeps pouring out of him more and more.
This is too creepy!
It's pitch black, like a bottomless pit.
What if it sucks us up?
Everyone make a run for it!
Get out of here!
Run to the forest! Run to the coast!
Just get away, quick!
Darkness is gravity.
It swallows everything around it.
Even light itself can't escape.
Its power is infinite.
That's nice.
But it's nowhere near me.
You sure you got the hang of this?
Calm down.
I'm not aiming at you yet.
You'll be glad when you
see what I do to this town?
Let's go!
Hotel, it's being
swallowed into the earth!
Why is he doing this?
What's going on?
Within these shadows lies a limitless
vow to compress anything and everything.
To crush whatever they touch.
This is a nightmare!
My home!
But that's just the beginning.
Now I'll show you what
happened to that town.
Or whatever's left of it, I should say.
Liberation!
It's all gone.
Nothing left but power.
So do you get it now, Ace?
This was what I was willing
to tell a friend for.
Firefly.
Fiery dog.
The darkness part I get,
but this not so much.
I wonder what's going on here.
If you're a Loki attack, that
shouldn't hurt you, or rather,
it shouldn't even hit you.
I already told you,
my darkness swallows everything
around it, whether it's punches,
blades, bullets, lightning, or fire.
Unlike you, I can't just turn into
an element and dodge an attack.
And the pain I absorb when I get hit is
much greater than what a normal human feels.
But the trade-off for that
inconvenience is more than worth it,
because there happens to be
one other thing I can absorb.
Black Vortex!
First,
I use the gravity of darkness to pull a
Devil Fruit power holder into my grasp.
Too strong!
And then when I touch them
You're smart if you figured
out the secret yet, huh?
It can't be
It's been so long since you've been hit,
I bet you forgot how much it hurts, Ace.
But you understand now, you
understood the second I grabbed you.
Not only can my darkness pull you in, it
can also absorb your Devil Fruit power!
In other words, as long as
they're in contact with me,
someone with Devil Fruit powers is
no different than a normal human.
Logia, Snow, Parameathia...
All those with Devil Fruit powers who have
become dependent on them
are in for a surprise.
One little touch will remind
them how weak they really are.
Then all I have to do is
avoid you if you think you
can escape gravity that
easily I'd like to see you try
That bastard almost broke my neck.
His ability is going to be a
bigger pain than I thought.
Crossfire!
Banana Rock is falling.
Nothing's safe anymore.
No one should have this kind of power.
Who are these monsters?
Forget about the town.
They'll destroy the entire island.
We're done for.
This is quite a surprise.
Most Devil Fruit power
holders with one such as his!
Would be rendered ineffective as soon as
their trump card was taken away from them.
Not so with Ace.
His powers are not a crutch
but an aid to his own talents.
We should expect no less from
one of Whitebeard's commanders.
We're at the crossroads of fate.
It's no coincidence that
these men have been brought
together.
Everything falls before darkness.
Even you can only struggle for so long.
Still finishing you off here
would be a waste of your talent.
Don't
If I surrender to you, then I could
never call myself a man again.
I won't submit and I won't live
with regrets no matter what.
You got that stupid?
Once you die, your morals are useless.
I'm sorry you can't understand that, Ace.
Cardass, take care!
Green Flame Commandment!
Flame Emperor!
The sun against darkness, huh?
Only one can win!
I'll make Whitebeard the king.
Or die trying.
There!
Although no one realized it at the time,
The duel at Benero Island
that day was not merely
a struggle between
Whitebeard and Blackbeard.
It was a catalyst.
This was the beginning of a chain of
events that could change the world.